Guide to the Louise Crane and Victoria Kent Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize and Other Storage, 0.71; (3 boxes)
  - Oversize
    - Crane family photograph album (Series I), 1960s (Box 38 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified, portraits (Series I), 1940; 2 (Box 38 (Oversize))
    - Vittorio Rieti, Sonata A Dieci (Series II), 1983; 2 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    Conditions Governing Access
    Box 39: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Glass negatives (Series I), undated (Box 39)
  - Oversize Rolls
    - Printed material (Series III), undated (Box 40 Roll)